-[insects chirping]
-[rumbling]
[dinosaurs bellowing]
[thudding]
[roars, screeches]
[alarm blaring]
[all panting]
[male voice] Attention. All park-goers
must report to the South Ferry Dock
for immediate evacuation.
-Last ferry departs in two hours.
-[panting continues]
That's it? No explanations?
That's all we get?
[Darius panting]
We have to move. The only way
we're gonna make it is if we run.
-Um...
-[Yasmina grunting]
Are we sure that's the best way
to get there?
I'm fine.
I've competed with a torn ACL.
You should be way more worried
about Ben and Bumpy.
[Ben panting]
What we should all be worried about
is catching a boat out of here
and, naturally, we have a problem.
We're here.
The docks are on the southern tip
of the island.
Even if we ran at peak Yaz speed,
there's no way we'd make
the last boat out.
You don't know that.
[scoffs] Yes, I do.
I memorized the evacuation plan
on the ferry ride over.
[all groan]
Okay, so we need another way.
Um...
Can we use those somehow?
Or send someone to tell the ferry people
to wait?
-Or...
-Or make a few jetpacks real quick?
Oh! We should befriend a unicorn!
Face it. It's hopeless.
[automated voice] We will be arriving
at Main Street--
-your destination for fine dining...
-Is that...?
...and shopping at Jurassic World.
Followed by stops
at the Jurassic World Lagoon
and the South Ferry Dock.
Monorail, what-what!
-Mm, nicely played, Universe.
-Hurry!
[all panting]
[Darius] We gotta move!
[both panting]
It's nice havin' some company back here
for once.
I'm fine.
[sighs]
[panting]
-[Kenji exclaims]
-[laughing]
[Brooklynn] Oh, no.
Shh!
-[growling]
-[gasps, pants]
[whispers] Move.
[growling continues]
-[snarls]
-[all gasp]
[gasps]
[grunts]
-[grunts]
-[clatters]
[snarls, growls]
[growls]
[gasps]
[Yasmina pants]
[gasping]
[sighs]
Mon--!
Shh!
[automated voice] Welcome to
the Jurassic World Lagoon.
-Next stop, Ferry Landing!
-[roars]
-[Darius] Run!
-[Ben whimpers]
-[roars]
-[yelps, pants]
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
[Ben screaming]
-[gasps]
-[Yasmina grunts]
-[grunts, pants]
-[roars]
[automated voice] Please stand clear
of the closing doors.
[Kenji grunts]
[Ben and Yasmina grunting]
-[whimpers]
-[grunting]
-[snarling]
-[Darius] Ben! Out of the way!
-[Yasmina whimpers]
-[roars]
[Ben and Yasmina scream]
-[whimpers]
-[roars]
-Please stand-- Please stand--
-Do not let those doors close!
[roaring]
-[Yasmina grunting]
-[roars]
[thuds]
-[grunts]
-[Ben yelps]
-[Kenji grunts]
-[Yasmina pants]
Doors closing.
[roaring]
No way.
Something bad always happens
when we think we're safe.
Watch. The doors are gonna open.
-[scoffs]
-Oh, okay,
then, the train's gonna stop
because that's how this works.
I'm pretty sure we're safe now.
Well, we were until you said that.
[Dave] I'll check here,
you check the stadium.
[Roxie] Kids?
-Darius?
-[Dave] Brooklynn?
[Roxie] Anybody here?
[panting]
Oh, no.
They made it out!
These look both posh and tacky enough
to be something Kenji would wear.
[Dave sighs]
They're okay. I know it.
[automated voice] Welcome to
the Jurassic World Lagoon.
The kids? They're alive!
Hey, guys!
-[Roxie] Hey!
-Kids! Kids! Dang it.
[male voice] Attention.
All park-goers must report
to the South Ferry Dock
for immediate evacuation.
Last ferry departs in 90 minutes.
-They're headed to the docks!
-Then it's time to ship out!
[roaring]
Or let's just go.
[roars]
[crickets chirping]
[Darius panting]
[sighs] It's over.
Guys, we did it.
We're going home.
Whoo-hoo!
-[gasps]
-[Bumpy squeals]
Yeah! Whoo!
-[Darius laughs]
-Whoo!
-Yeah!
-Yes!
Yeah!
[all laughing]
-Finally!
-Alrighty!
It's cool, man. We're good.
We'll be at the main dock soon.
This calls for a celebration.
I might be able to help with that.
Stashed a few treats for the road.
-Ooh, sweet!
-I'm starving!
Our little Ben is useful.
[all retching, spitting]
[Sammy] This is nasty.
Get it off! Get it off!
Ben, someone stole your candy bars
and put dirt in 'em.
They're carob bars.
They pair perfectly with--
Carob juice.
Awesome.
Carob is nature's chocolate.
Just as delicious, with none of the sugar
or caffeine.
What's wrong with sugar and caffeine?
First thing I'm gonna do when I get home
is hug my espresso machine.
I may never let go.
You know... [clears throat] I've often
described myself as a tall, hot drink.
[all scoffing]
-Come on, man.
-Gross.
You could never be coffee.
[scoffs] I could be coffee.
I cannot wait to be home.
Once my ankle's better,
it's back to training.
And I guess finding
a new corporate sponsor,
since mine was Jurassic World.
But you know...
It's gonna be weird for things
to be normal again.
Like, are video games
gonna seem boring now? [chuckles]
How about you? What's the first thing
you'll do when you get home?
Depends on which wing of our mansion
you're talkin' about.
East wing is usually off limits,
but Dad and Candy are away on business,
so I guess I'll go downstairs
to our bowling alley. [chuckles]
Staff always lets me win.
Life of a VIP.
So, what have you missed, Ben?
[Kenji] Oh. Let me guess,
you can't wait to get home to your closet
of dork pouches.
-[Brooklynn and Sammy chuckle]
-Ha, ha. Very funny.
Seriously, Ben, you've had juice boxes
for days!
How much stuff can you fit in that thing?
One, lots, and two,
obviously the first thing I'm gonna do
when I get back is restock it.
[all laughing]
Check it out.
[imitates lightsaber powering up]
[Ben and Brooklynn grunt]
I found the first thing at Jurassic World
that works!
[chuckles] Still works.
I still can't believe how much went wrong.
[chuckles]
Like that time we almost got eaten?
Which time?
How was there more than one time?
Let's all raise our carob juice.
A toast!
To not getting eaten!
-To not getting eaten!
[slurping]
[grunts] Ugh!
[Yasmina groans]
-[spits]
-[slurps, sighs]
[Brooklynn shudders]
-To no more running away!
-[slurps]
-[Darius chuckles]
[Brooklynn] Hmm.
Mm-mm.
[slurps, sighs]
To the return of a low-level gnawing dread
rather than an all-encompassing
impending doom!
Why not!
-[Brooklynn] To what Ben said!
-[Kenji] Bad doom versus normal doom!
-I got one. [gasps]
-[explosion]
[all grunt]
What was that?
It sounded like an explosion.
-Ugh! Not again!
-I don't see anything.
I don't think it was near us.
We're okay. We're still okay.
[Bumpy groans]
I know camp wasn't what we thought
it was gonna be.
But after everything we went through,
at least we're leavin' this place
with five new friends!
To the six of us being best friends
for life!
Clink!
"No added sugars," wow.
[Sammy] Guys?
Hello?
Wait, do you guys not see us as friends?
I mean... [sighs]
Doesn't it usually take
more than a few days
to become friends with someone?
We were thrown together at random.
We have nothing in common.
That's not true!
We've been through more together
than most friends have in a lifetime.
And now that it's over, what are the odds
that we'll ever see each other again?
[automated voice] Coming up on the right,
you'll see our world-renowned
18-hole, dinosaur-themed
golf course.
It's one of the many wonders
that makes this park so very Jurassic.
[chuckles] What does that even mean?
I thought I knew.
My whole life, I had this idea
of Jurassic World.
My dad used to say this place was,
"All-osaurus and a bag of chips."
He was so corny.
Um, was?
So, your dad is...
I'm sorry, Darius.
Ugh! "Sorry." Nice one,
Sammy, ya ding-dong!
-Like "sorry" could begin to--
-It's okay.
Hey, at least your dad never saw
what a dumpster fire this place turned out
to be, huh?
Ow! What?
I meant it's cool that Darius and his dad
were so close.
I could count on one hand
the number of times me and my dad
have done... anything.
Kenji, that's just real sad.
Yeah.
Did I mention I have a bowling alley?
[Ben] Dang it!
Come on, it's gotta be here somewhere.
Oh! [scoffs]
Bumpy stepped in something icky
and I'm low on sanitizer.
It's fine. I can make more.
Ben, why are you here?
What he means is--
Eh, well, you're scared of dinosaurs,
and the outdoors,
and sometimes the indoors, and germs.
Whipped cream for some reason?
The way it moves. [shudders]
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
What's the deal?
[Bumpy squeals]
My mom works for Mr. Masrani.
She got me into camp.
Said it would be a great way for me
to "face my fears." It's been a nightmare!
I'm sick of being scared all the time.
And of running,
and of almost getting eaten,
and... and of holding everyone back.
I just can't do... this.
[Bumpy groans]
[Ben] But it's not all bad.
If I hadn't come,
I-- I never would have met--
-[crashing]
-[all gasp]
-[all grunt]
[Darius panting]
-[crashing]
-[all yell]
Guys, we gotta turn off the lights!
-[smashing]
-[Darius grunting]
-[gasps]
-[screeches]
Flying reptiles are basically seabirds.
They're attracted to shiny,
moving objects,
-and with all these lights on--
-We're a shiny, moving object!
[screeches]
[screams]
[Kenji panting]
What should I do?
-Just keep out of the way!
-[smashing continues]
-[screeching]
-[whimpering]
[Yasmina and Sammy yelp]
[grunting]
-[whimpering]
-[grunting continues]
[electricity buzzes]
[squawking]
[screeching]
-[whimpers, screams]
-[screeches]
[grunts] Brooklynn, you're with Yaz.
Sammy, help Ben and Bumpy across!
[Yasmina pants] Whoa!
[grunts, thuds]
[Bumpy grunts]
[screeching]
[automated voice] Smile!
You're at Jurassic World.
We hope you're having...
[distorted voice] a Jurassic time.
[yelps, grunts]
[Bumpy squeals]
-[crashing]
-[grunting, groaning]
[gasps]
At least now we know
what that boom was earlier.
-I told you--
-[Brooklynn] Don't.
If we don't switch tracks
or stop this car right now,
we're gonna hit that thing, full speed!
The front car,
there's control panels there!
VIP Tour, I was eight, they let me drive.
[grunts] No, no, no!
-[Ben whimpering]
-[Bumpy groans]
[all grunting]
-[grunts, sighs]
-[screeching]
I'm gonna get to the control car
through there.
-You're gonna what?
-You can't go out there!
[sputters] That's where
the flying whatevers are!
We don't have a choice! Me and--
-I'm the only one who can fit.
-[screeches]
-[yelps]
-[all yelp]
[Bumpy groans]
You're gonna be okay.
Distract the flock while I crawl over
the top to the control car.
Use the flashlights, keep them away from--
-[hatch squeaks]
-[all gasp]
[Bumpy squeals]
[gasps] Ben!
Ben, what are you doing?
[grunts]
I can do this! Just distract them!
-[pants, screams]
-[screeches]
Come on! We have to keep them away
from Ben!
[pants]
[all panting]
[screeches]
I can do this.
[grunts]
-[all panting]
-[screeching]
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[console trilling]
[whimpering]
-[bangs]
-[screeches]
[panting]
-[screams]
[crashing]
[grunting]
[crashes]
[screeching]
[laughing, whooping]
-[pants, sighs]
-[Brooklynn] Yeah!
[all chanting] Ben, Ben,
Ben, Ben, Ben, Ben!
-[Ben laughs]
-[Bumpy groans]
You saved us, Ben.
I didn't know you had it in you.
[glass shatters]
-Ben!
-[Ben screaming]
[grunting]
-[Ben gasps, whimpers]
-[grunting]
-Oh, no!
-[grunting, screaming]
[Ben] Help!
-Hang on!
-[grunts] Darius! Darius! Darius!
No! [grunts]
No! [screams]
[theme music playing]